So,what is this?
這是什麼？
Googlie Worm.
扭扭蟲
And this?
這個呢？
Glow Pop Jiggly Jam.
毛毛球
It's so funny!
好好玩喔
What's this?
這是什麼？
A hunk of sandwich from last year.
去年剩的一塊三明治
Geller's got one hooked! Looks like a big one!
蓋勒釣到了！看來是條大魚
It's the classic struggle between man
經典的人魚大戰…
Someone knocked over a lamp.
有人撞倒一盞檯燈
You know what'll be great about the fishing trip?
這次去釣魚最棒的是
When my Dad asks,"What are you doing with your life?"...
到了湖中央 爸會問我「你都在忙什麼」
...I can say,"I'm doing a movie with Charlton Heston.
我可以說 我要跟卻爾登希斯頓演電影
What about you?"
你呢？
太棒了
Don't stop having fun just because I'm here.
別因為我出來就低氣壓
Kathy didn't cheat on all of you.
凱西沒有背叛你們
Well,except you.
除了你
You know what is so sweet? Those birds have not left his side the whole time.
最感人的是 那兩隻雞鴨一直跟著他
Yeah,I wish that rooster were dead.
那只公雞怎麼不死
You shouldn't leave Chandler alone. They broke up only two days ago.
喬伊，你不該丟下錢德 他跟凱西才分手2天
Go fishing next week.
下周再去釣魚吧
There's nothing I can do. He's still in his sweats.
我幫不上忙，他還穿著運動褲
That's only phase one.
現在才第一階段
I'll be back for phase two. I'd never miss that.
我第二階段會回來 我從不錯過第二階段
Phase two?
什麼第二階段？
Getting drunk and going to a strip club.
喝個爛醉，上脫衣舞廳
How does going there make him better?
那樣怎麼會有幫助？
There are naked ladies there.
那裡有裸女
Then to phase three: seeing yourself with other women.
然後就是第三階段 對別的女人產生性幻想
There are naked ladies there too.
那個階段也有裸女
Would you give me one minute,please?
讓我清靜一下好嗎？
The One with Joey's Dirty Day
本集播出：「失戀大作戰」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
These will match the jacket you picked out last week?
這跟你上星期挑的外套配？
There we go.
這就對了…
There it is.
就是這樣…
You know what I need? Gloves.
你知道我需要什麼？手套
Brown leather dress gloves.
棕色的皮手套
Well,let's see....
好，我看看...
This one is large.
這隻手是大號
And this one....
這隻手…
Also large?
也是大號？
Two larges coming right up.
對，兩隻大號的手套馬上來
Hello.
-Damn you. -Could I have a moment?
瑞秋，耽誤你一下
My niece,you see, is in town from London.
我的姪女從倫敦來玩
Shropshire,but you know.
其實是什羅普郡
She's about your age,I'd say.
她跟你差不多大
Anyway,I have tickets for the opera. Die Fledermaus.
總之我有兩張歌劇的票 「蝙蝠」
Would you like to keep her company tonight?
你今晚願意陪她嗎？
Sure. You got it!
好，沒問題 太好了
Count me in. Me. Fledermaus. Great!
算我一份 我和「蝙蝠」，太棒了
Yes,of course. Thank you so very much.
好，謝謝，謝謝，謝謝你
So?
所以…？
怎樣？
-Gloves? -Sorry,I'll be right back.
手套？ 對喔，我馬上去拿
Actually,I got to take off.
其實我該走了
I was curious. Do you have plans tonight?
不曉得你今晚有沒有事？
No,nothing!
沒有，沒事
I invested in a nightclub. It opens tonight. Want to come?
我投資的夜總會今晚開幕 你要去嗎？
That would be great!
好啊，太棒了
You're into hard-core S & M,right?
你喜歡性虐待的主題吧？
-Well,I guess. -I'm kidding.
應該… 開玩笑的
I'll put you on the VlP list. Look for me.
我會先到，我會把你列為貴賓 進來找我
Great! You bet.
好，沒問題
I'll see you tonight.
晚上見 好
-I almost forgot the tickets. -What?
差點忘了給你票 什麼？
For you and Emily. Tonight. Die Fledermaus.
你和艾蜜莉，今晚 「蝙蝠」
Oh,right.
對喔
You'll like it. It has two out of the three tenors.
你一定會喜歡 三大男高音去了兩個
I can't believe Kathy did this to me.
凱西居然這樣對我
I really thought she was the one.
我真的以為我要定下來了
I'll tell you what.
告訴你們
I'm not getting out of this chair. Ever!
我再也不離開這張椅子了
From now on,this chair is the one!
以後我要定在這張椅子上
You know what else is the one? My sweatpants.
還有這條運動褲
Just take the sweats off,okay?
別這樣，把運動褲脫掉
Take them off and we'll have some fun.
脫掉，我們來玩
Wow,and I can't resist that line. That's why I never wear sweatpants.
我抗拒不了這個誘惑 所以我都不穿運動褲
Did you catch any fish?
有釣到大魚嗎？
You guys have no idea.
說出來嚇死你們
-You stink! -Are you kidding?
你好臭 搞什麼
Three days without a shower. Plus,I fell in a big tub of worms!
我3天沒洗澡 還掉進一桶魚餌裡
How's he doing?
他怎麼樣？
He hasn't left that chair in two days.
坐在那裡坐了2天
Hey,buddy,how's it going?
兄弟，你還好嗎？
You see? He just needed his pal to come home.
好兄弟回家就沒事了
I got to memorize my lines.
我得背台詞
Me and Charlton Heston, bright and early tomorrow,baby!
明天一早 要和卻爾登希斯頓演戲
What's the matter?
怎麼了？
Joshua invited me to this fancy club opening tonight.
約書亞約我參加夜總會開幕
But I already told Mr. Waltham...
但我已經答應沃森先生
...that I would take his niece to the dumb old opera.
要帶他的姪女去看老掉牙歌劇
So,what are you going to do?
能怎麼辦呢？
-I don't know. -No! Help me!
我不知道 不行，救救我
-I can't. I have to work. -Phoebe?
我不行，我要工作 菲比？
I would,but I get my morning sickness in the evening.
我很想，但我都在晚上害喜
Unless she wants to spend the night holding my hair back for me.
除非她想整晚幫我撈住頭髮
You guys,come on! I have to meet Joshua.
拜託啦，我一定要去找約書亞
It's my one chance for him to see the "fun" Rachel.
這樣他才能看到有趣的瑞秋
The "wouldn't it be great if she were my wife?" Rachel.
「娶來當老婆會很棒」的瑞秋
Are Joey and Chandler back?
喬伊和錢德回來了嗎？
Chandler's still in phase one, and Joey's that thing you smell.
錢德還在第一階段 喬伊就是臭味的來源
So....
所以…？
No.
不要
Come on!
拜託啦
-She's here. -Wait,wait.
應該是她 等一下
Ross,please?
羅斯，拜託啦
You want me to take some girl I've never met to the opera...
你要我帶一個不認識的女生 去看歌劇
...so you can go to a club and flirt with some guy?
好讓你去夜總會 跟某個男人打情罵俏？
That is a toughie.
真難決定啊
She's looking down the hall.
她在看走廊
She looked right at me.
她在看我
You can't see people through that hole,can you?
這樣看是看不到的，對吧？
I'll be right there! Okay,Ross,please.
馬上來 羅斯，拜託啦
I thought we had moved on.
我以為我們已經放得開了
I thought we could be happy for each other.
我以為我們可以彼此祝福了
I mean,was that just me?
難道只有我是？
All right,I'll do it.
好吧
Thank you,thank you.
謝謝你，謝謝
Emily. I'm Rachel Greene.
艾蜜莉 我是瑞秋葛林
Thank goodness!
謝天謝地
There's been a teeny change of plans. I'm not free tonight
計劃有小小的變動 我晚上沒空，所以…
Really?
是嗎？
I must've missed your call,though I didn't leave the flat all day.
太好了，我一定是沒接到電話 雖然我整天都沒出門
Well,l
我…
That's not rude. It's in keeping with the trip...
不，這也沒什麼 我來到這裡
...where I've been run down by one of your wiener carts...
先是被你們的熱狗車撞倒
...and been strip-searched at the airport.
在機場又被脫衣服搜身
Apparently,I look like someone who's got cocaine stuffed up their bum.
顯然我長得就像 屁股裡塞了可卡因
I think you look great.
我覺得你很漂亮啊
Good night. It was very nice to meet you.
再見，很高興認識你
I'll get her.
我去追她
Please,hurry.
快去 好
Don't you just love the way they talk?
他們講話好好玩
-What? -The baby kicked!
怎麼了？ 寶寶在踢
Oh,my God.
No,wait. The elastic in my underwear busted.
不對，是內褲的鬆緊帶斷了
Oh,my God! I overslept!
完了，我睡過頭了
I was supposed to be on the set half an hour ago!
通告是半小時前，我得趕快
You can't go like that! You stink!
你不能這樣去，你好臭
I fell asleep. Now I don't have time!
我睡著忘記洗澡 現在沒時間了
Just 10 blocks away. If I run,I'll make it.
才十條街，用跑的還來得及
Run 10 blocks. That'll help the smell.
跑十條街會更臭
Slow down! No,keep moving.
慢一點！不，你走吧
How did it go last night?
昨晚怎麼樣啊？
Well,I didn't see Joshua.
我沒見到約書亞
But I did punch a girl in the face.
但我揍了一個女生一拳
The whole night was horrible. It was pouring.
昨晚真的很倒霉，雨下得很大
There was no Rachel Greene on the list. But there was a Rachel Greep.
到了現場名單上沒有瑞秋葛林 但有一個瑞秋葛皮
So did you get to meet her?
你有見到她嗎？
There is no Rachel Greep. But this girl overheard us.
根本沒這個人 但有個女生聽到了
And she said,"I'm Rachel Greep!" And he let her in.
大叫「我就是瑞秋葛皮」 結果她就進去了
So you hit her?
所以你揍她？
No,she was already in.
不是，她已經進去了
This big bitch behind me tried to steal my umbrella...
不過後面有個肥婆想偷我的傘
...so I clocked her.
我扁了她
All I wanted was a few hours...
真是的，我只想在工作之餘
...outside of work to see Joshua...
跟約書亞相處一下
...so he could go ahead and start falling in love with me.
好讓他有機會愛上我
Pheebs.
菲
Honey,that's your name.
那是你的名字
That's short for Phoebe? I thought that's what we called each other.
我以為那是我們之間的匿稱
-You're wearing pants! -That's right.
你穿上褲子了 沒錯
Where are the guys? I'm ready to get drunk and see strippers.
男生呢？我要買醉看脫衣舞了
It's 9:30 a.m.
才早上9點半
They got a breakfast buffet.
那裡有早餐吃到飽
喂…羅斯
Let me talk to him!
讓我跟他說
-Oh,my God! -Can't I just?
天哪 我能不能…
-It's my phone and she's shush -Please!
我的電話她還噓我 別吵啦！
What's he saying?
他說什麼？
He's with Emily in Vermont.
他跟艾蜜莉在佛蒙特投宿
What? Oh,my God!
什麼？天哪
Who the hell is Emily? No.
艾蜜莉是誰？不！
When we first met her, she was soaking,her feet were wet....
剛見面的時候 她從頭到腳都濕透了
Who wouldn't be miserable?
任誰都會心情不好
I'm telling you,once l got her into a dry pair of shoes...
我一讓她換上干的鞋子
...she was a totally different person.
她就完全變了
They're in Vermont? How did this happen?
他們在佛蒙特？怎麼會？
How'd he end up in Vermont with that witch?
他怎麼會跟那個巫婆去佛蒙特
Maybe she doesn't hit him all the time.
也許她沒有一直打他吧
There's a deer outside eating fruit from the orchard!
羅斯，快來 外面有只馴鹿在吃果園的水果
I got to go! There's a deer eating fruit from the orchard!
我要掛了 外面有只馴鹿在吃果園的水果
He had to go. There was a deer eating fruit from the orchard.
他掛了 外面有只馴鹿在吃果園的水果
I don't get this. She was horrible!
我不懂，她很機車耶
I'm going to go stand over there.
我要去站在那邊
Why do you care?
你幹嘛這麼在乎？
I don't care.
我才不在乎
I'm just upset that I'm getting nowhere with Joshua.
我只是很氣我跟約書亞沒進展
You do not just meet someone and go flitting off to Vermont!
但哪有人一認識 就跑去佛蒙特的
When you first met Barry, you flitted off to Vail.
你和貝利一認識就跑去維爾
Could you,just for once...
你能不能偶爾有一次
...not remember every little thing?
不要什麼小事都記得
So you know,when's he getting back?
他什麼時候回來？
A couple of days.
過兩天吧
I knew something like this would happen.
我就知道會這樣
What are you doing?
你幹什麼？
You can't go back a phase!
錢德，你不能讓階段倒流
You're thinking about time. You can't go back in time.
可以，時間才不能倒流
Why don't you do your phase two strip club thing with us?
我們跟你去進行第二階段好了
We can be guys!
對呀，我們可以當男生
No,you can't.
你們不行
Let us be guys! Maybe we want to be guys.
讓我們當嘛，也許我們想當
No,you don't. You'd be all hairy and wouldn't live as long.
你們才不想，全身是毛還短命
Would you just stop being such a wuss and get those off?
別這麼孬種 把運動褲脫掉
And come with us and watch naked girls dance!
跟我們去看裸女跳舞
Okay.
好
I'm sorry.
對不起
（銀杯片廠）
Joey Tribbiani. I'm here.
我是喬伊崔比亞尼，我來了
Calm down,we got time. We're running late.
別急，來得及，進度有點落後
All set.
Look at that. Charlton Heston eating licorice.
你看，卻爾登希斯頓在嚼甘草
Yeah,he loves them. I've never seen him with
他很愛嚼甘草，老是…
What the hell is that? What smells so bad?
搞什麼？ 什麼東西這麼臭？
You.
你
I could see why you would think that. But you know who it is?
難怪你會這麼想，不過,你知道其實是誰？
You?
你？
No,no. It's Heston.
不，是希斯頓
What?
什麼？
He reeks like he went on a three-day fishing trip,then ate licorice.
他臭得好像去釣了3天魚 現在還嚼甘草
No way. He's the only one with a shower in his dressing room.
不可能 只有他的休息室有浴室
Really? A shower?
真的？浴室？
Which room might that be?
是哪一間？
The one with "Heston" on it.
門口有寫「希斯頓」的那間
Interesting.
有意思
I got some ones. You want to put them in her panties?
我換了零鈔 你要不要去塞她的小褲褲？
No,thanks,Mom!
不用了，娘
That.
抱歉
You have to put that out because I'm pregnant.
你得熄掉，我懷孕了
Maybe you and your baby ought to go to another strip club.
也許你和你的孩子應該去別家
It's not my baby.
這才不是我的孩子
Very good.
很好
Really good. I enjoyed it. Very exotic.
太棒了，我喜歡，很火辣
I just checked our messages and Joshua didn't call.
我查過留言，約書亞沒打來
You'd think he'd be worried about me not showing up.
我還以為我沒去他會擔心
You know what makes it worse?
更糟的是
Ross is all happy in Vermont.
羅斯正在佛蒙特風流快活
Come on,look where you are!
拜託，你在看脫衣舞耶
Another round of daiquiris.
再來一輪
Virgin for me.
記得我要汽水
Don't let me leave without the name of that carpet guy.
記得提醒我問那個人的名字
凱倫，還有，你最好…
Come on!
拜託！
You know what? I'll go home and call Kathy.
算了，我要回家打給凱西
If it'll help.
如果有用的話
That was a test. In a few hours,I'll be drunk.
不，那是個考驗 再過幾小時我會喝醉...
I'll want to call her. You'll have to stop me.
...想打給她 你們得阻止我
Then I'll be so drunk, I'll want to call Janice.
接著我會爛醉到想打給珍妮絲
You should! How is she?
你是該打，她好嗎？
I think somebody needs another lap dance.
有人需要再來一次腿舞喔
Who's in there?
誰在裡面？
How you doing?
你好嗎？
Who in the hell are you?
你是誰？
Would you believe me if I said I was Kirk Douglas?
我說寇克道格拉斯 你不會信吧？
Put some pants on,kid, so I can kick your butt.
把褲子穿上，我好踹你的屁股
No,wait. You don't understand.
不，等等，你有所不知
I'm an actor.
我是個演員
Joey Tribbiani. I'm doing a scene with you today.
喬伊崔比亞尼 今天跟你有一場戲
And I stink!
但是我很臭（演得很爛）
You're in this picture?
你有演這部片？
I'm a cop who won't work with you because you're a loose cannon.
對，我演不肯跟你合作的警察 因為你很我行我素
Anyway,I'm really sorry.
總之我很抱歉
But I stink.
但我真的很臭（演得很爛）
Joey,right?
喬伊是吧？
Every actor,one time or another
每個演員或多或少…
Every actor thinks he stinks.
都會覺得自己爛
Even Laurence Olivier sometimes thought he stank.
連勞倫斯奧立佛 有時也會這麼想
Bob Redford won't even watch himself.
勞勃瑞福根本不看自己演戲
You don't understand.
不，你沒聽懂
Listen to me.
聽我說
I don't know one actor worth his salt...
每一個好演員
...who,one time in his career, didn't say,"God,I stink!"
在演藝生涯中都曾說過 「天哪，我真爛」
I just did a scene out there. First take,I stunk the place up.
我剛拍完一場戲 第一次我演得爛透了
The important thing, and you must remember...
重要的是你要記住
...no matter how badly you think you stink...
不管你認為自己有多爛
...you must never,ever bust into my dressing room and use my shower!
也不能闖進我的休息室 用我的浴室
Do you understand me?
懂了嗎？
-Yes,sir. I'm very sorry. -Wait a minute!
是，很抱歉 等等
Take your pants.
把褲子帶走
Sorry. I'm really sorry.
對不起，很抱歉
What a business.
演藝圈
We did okay at the strip club,right?
我們表現得還好吧？
Great. Thanks to you, the hottest waitress is quitting...
好得很 你們讓最性感的服務生 要辭職...
...to teach the third grade!
...去當小學老師
-He still hasn't called. -Who,Josh?
他居然還沒打來 約許嗎？
It's Joshua.
是約書亞
-He doesn't like "Josh"? -No,I don't.
他不喜歡約許？ 是我不喜歡
I'm going to put my sweats back on.
我要把運動褲換回來
You know what? You were right.
不要啦！你說得對
We weren't great at being guys. You know why?
我們當男生當得不好 你知道為什麼？
Because we're girls.
因為我們是女生
-You know what girls are good at? -Stripping!
你知道女生最擅長什麼？ 跳脫衣舞
No,listening!
不，是傾聽
Sit.
坐下
Maybe it would really,really help if you would just talk.
如果你肯一吐為快 或許就沒事了
Yeah,come on. What's going on in there?
是啊，你的心在想什麼？
And you know,if you want to cry, that's okay too.
你想哭也沒關係
I'm going to have to ask you all to leave.
我要請你們都離開
Forget it. We tried, but phase three is a lost cause.
算了，我們試過了 但第三階段沒希望了
Those strippers were hot,and l couldn't picture myself with them.
那些舞孃都很辣 我卻無法產生性幻想
They really were pretty, weren't they?
她們真的很漂亮
-I liked that fighter pilot one. -Candy?
我喜歡一號戰鬥機駕駛 糖糖？
She was so spunky!
她好有勁 對啊
I think if I were going to be with a woman...
要是我要跟女人在一起…
...it'd be with someone like Michelle.
我會選蜜雪兒那型的
She was just so petite.
她好嬌小
For me,it would have to be Chantal.
我會選香妲
沒錯 天哪
She had the smoothest skin.
她的皮膚好嫩
I stuck that dollar in her G-string and grazed her thigh
我塞錢給她時 手擦過她的大腿…
Phase three! I just achieved phase three!
第三階段！ 我進入第三階段了
I am totally picturing you with all those women!
真的？ 我可以想像你們跟她們在一起
That's not phase three.
那不是第三階段
Well,I'm there too!
我也在場
Are we all together in a group?
我們在開性派對嗎？
Stop it,you're killing me!
別說了，我快瘋了
I think I moved on to phase four!
我進入第四階段了
-What is that? -I don't want a relationship ever!
那是什麼？ 我再也不想談戀愛
I just want sex with strippers and my friends!
只想跟脫衣舞孃和朋友上床
Come on.
來嘛
Let me see that smile.
讓我看看你的笑容
I don't want to.
我不想笑
Please?
拜託啦？
I wanted to go to the strip club!
人家想看脫衣舞嘛
You'll have plenty of chances.
你有的是機會
There are thousands of women out there, just waiting to screw me over.
有成千上萬的女人等著傷害我
Yeah,all right.
好吧
How was Vermont?
這趟玩得怎樣？
Emily is...
艾蜜莉真是…
...incredible. There are no words to describe her.
...太棒了 她好得無法形容
The whole weekend was like a dream.
整個週末就像一場夢
And you! Rach!
還有你，瑞秋
You were so right.
你說得一點也沒錯
What?
什麼？
What you said about us finally being in a place...
你說我們總算到了一個
...where we could really be happy for each other.
可以彼此祝福的階段
I admit,I wasn't quite there.
我原本沒那麼放得開
The thought of you and that Josh guy
想到你和那個約許…
Joshua.
約書亞
Joshua guy at that club, dancing,having a good time.
約書亞，在俱樂部裡跳舞狂歡
And the thought of it kind of....
我就覺得…
You know? But now!
你懂嗎？但現在…
But now,I'm totally there.
我完全放開了
I'm finally where you are.
我終於跟你一樣了
Thank goodness!
謝天謝地
And thank you for Emily.
謝謝你把艾蜜莉介紹給我
No problem. I'm so glad I could help,you know?
不客氣，我樂得幫忙
I'm happy for you.
我很替你開心
Happy for you.
我才替你開心
Oh,no,happy for you.
不，我才替你開心
All right. Here's what we'll do.
好，接下來是這樣
You are going to take off my clothes.
你幫我脫衣服
You two,go get the oils.
你們兩個去拿精油
And you,just constantly scream...
你就一直興奮的叫
..."Chandler's the king! Chandler's the king!"
「吾王錢德萬歲！」
I want to be with her. I like her.
我想跟她在一起，我喜歡她
That's fine. Go with your instincts!
沒問題，大家隨意
What am I doing again?
我要做什麼？
Pay attention. I could wake up at any moment.
專心一點，我隨時都會醒來
I'm Joshua. I'm here to pick up Rachel.
我是約書亞，我來接瑞秋
That's not Joshua.
他不是約書亞
What do you want from me? I never met the guy.
你想怎樣？我又沒見過他
I'm sorry you can't stay.
可惜你要走了
The rest of us have a lot of work to do.
我們還有很多事要忙
What are you doing?
你幹什麼？
All right,listen. I got to wake up.
好，我得醒過來